<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RoundDIsland</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lmk_information">LmkInformation</string>

    <string name="how_to_play_intro">Join in on the fun, explore Bermuda\'s most famous and historical landmarks!</string>
    <string name="how_to_play_info">\n1. Click start below\n
                                    \n2. Locate the Weekly Hunts\n
                                    \n3. Find and scan each location\n
                                    \n4. Head to one of our sponsors to claim your prize!</string>

    <string name="contact_us_overview">The 2018 TLF students created this app to give people something else to do during their time in Bermuda.
                                        \n\nThe Round D Island application has been designed for the use of tourists and locals to allow them to
                                        explore and learn about landmarks in Bermuda. Currently the app is only for the use of android devices.
                                        Individuals will be allowed to download the app from our website which will allow them to explore and learn
                                        about significant Bermudian landmarks.
                                        \n\nThe TLF program is an intensive 12-week summer internship where IT college students acquire experience
                                        in the ICT industry through classroom learning, team projects, fieldwork.
</string>
    <string name="contact_us_contact_info">Connectech\n41 Ceder Avenue\nHamilton HM02\nBermuda\n\n1.441.704.3677\n\ninfo@tlf.bm</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_info">
Privacy Policy
\n
\n
TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018 built the Round D\' Island app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by TLF Interns of 2018 at no cost and \n
is intended for use as is.
\n
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.
\n
We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices
\n
        with regards to your personal information, please contact us a <b><u><font color = "blue">rounddisland@gmail.com</font></u></b>
\n
When you visit our mobile application, and use our services, you trust us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this
\n
privacy notice, we describe our privacy policy. We seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what
\n
rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy policy \n
that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our App and our services.
\n
\n
<b>1. What information do we collect?</b>
\n
\n
Information collected through our Apps
\n
In short: we may collect information regarding your mobile device, push notifications, when you use our apps
\n
We do not collect any information. However, we do need access for the following:
\n
\n
<b>Mobile Device Access</b>. We will request access or permission to certain features from your mobile device, including your mobile device’s camera. If you wish to \n
change our access or permissions, you may do so in your device’s settings.
\n
<b>Push Notifications.</b> We may request to send you push notifications regarding your account or the mobile application. If you wish to opt-out from receiving
\n
these types of communications, you may turn them off in your device’s settings.
\n
\n
<b>2. Will your information be shared with anyone?</b>
\n
We do NOT collect any information from you therefore we will not share any information in any situation.
\n
\n
<b>3. How long do we keep your information?</b>
\n
We do NOT collect your information; therefore, no information will be stored.
\n
\n
<b>4. What are your privacy rights?</b>
\n
You may delete this application at any time. You may also remove access to camera and notifications
\n
\n
<b>5. Do we make updates to this policy?</b>
\n
In short: Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.
\n
We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “revised” date and the updated version will be \n
effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy policy, the app will send a notification directly. We encourage you to \n
review this privacy policy frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
\n
\n
<b>Terms &amp; Conditions</b>
\n
\n
By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the \n
app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source \n
code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, \n
copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018
\n
TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018] is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve \n
the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services \n
without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
\n
The Round D’ Island app does not store and process personal data that you have provided to us, in order to provide our Service. It’s your responsibility to \n
keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software \n
restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious \n
programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the Round D’ Island app won’t work properly or at all.
\n
You should be aware that there are certain things that TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018 will not take responsibility for. Certain functions \n
of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider, but TLF \n
(Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018 cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and \n
you don’t have any of your data allowance left.
\n
If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still \n
apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other \n
third-party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of \n
your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, \n
please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
\n
Along the same lines, TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018 cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make \n
sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of \n
2018 cannot accept responsibility
\n
With respect to TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear \n
in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we \n
can make it available to you. TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018 accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a \n
result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
\n
At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android the requirements for this system may change, and you’ll need to \n
download the updates if you want to keep using the app. TLF (Technology Leadership Forum) Interns of 2018 does not promise that it will always update the app \n
so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to \n
the application when offered to you, we may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination \n
to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the \n
app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.
\n
\n
<b>Changes to these Terms and Conditions</b>
\n
\n
We may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any \n
changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.
\n
\n
<b>Contact Us</b>
\n
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact us. <b><u><font color="blue">rounddisland@gmail.com</font></u></b></string>
    <string name="winpage_info">Congradulations\nYou have completed the weekly hunt.\n\nHead to one of our sponsors.\n\nShow your code(check the Challenges page for more info)
                                \n\n\nDisclaimer: In order for your code to be validated you <b>must</b> connected to Wifi</string>
</resources>
